thetechjournal.com 2019-05-20

# Privacy Policy – The Tech Journal

**Privacy Policy For _[TheTechJournal.com](http://thetechjournal.com/)_**  
The privacy of our visitors to _[TheTechJournal.com](http://thetechjournal.com/)_ is important to us. As a Technological News Site, [TheTechJournal.com](http://thetechjournal.com/) is committed to the security of your information and pledges to follow the terms set out in this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”).

 **Website Information Usage**  
We use web stat services and analytics software to track the referral, location, browser, operating system and screen resolution of our visitors, but not private information about each individual (such as your name or email address). E-mail addresses are only ever provided by the user voluntarily through the commenting process or via e-mail communications. Note: E-mail addresses that are entered in the required “e-mail” field in the comments area, are not publicly displayed. We aggregate user-specific information on which pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by readers, such as survey information and/or Website registrations. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Website in a technical fashion only and not sold to any third party unless mentioned explicitly.

 **Public Information**  
Our Website enables you to post information to be accessed by others through our comments. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data and attempt to contact you off the site. TheTechJournal.com cannot be held liable for any offsite communications that result from your posting of personal information on our site. If you do not wish to be contacted offsite by other _[TheTechJournal.com](http://thetechjournal.com/)_ visitors, do not give your e-mail address or website address in the content when leaving a comment. Please note: Although you are required to provide your e-mail address in the specified field when entering a comment, your e-mail address will only be available to TheTechJournal.com website administrators and will not be publicly visible. We have used Disqus platform for managing our Comments. Please Refer to their Policy & Terms for more details [here](http://docs.disqus.com/kb/terms-and-policies/). When you are commenting you have to agree to both our and Disqus’s terms.

 **Advertisers**  
Third-party advertisers featured on _[TheTechJournal.com](http://thetechjournal.com/)_ may collect tracking information in a different manner than is set out in this Privacy Policy. The only information that they will be able to track is basic Website usage information; e-mail addresses are not passed on to advertisers for any reason even if they are provided to _[TheTechJournal.com](http://thetechjournal.com/)_ voluntarily.

 **Affiliate Marketing**  
Our website contains some affiliate marketing links, which means we get paid commission on sales of those products or services we write about. Our editorial content is not influenced by advertisers or affiliate partnerships. We use a 3rd Party to enable these affiliate partnerships. You can read their [Privacy Policy](http://skimlinks.com/privacy-policy#users) and find more information on [the cookies they use](http://skimlinks.com/user-cookies).

 **Cookies**  
We use cookies to store visitor preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, customize Website content based on visitor browser type or other information that the visitor sends. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site. Google, through their Adsense Program, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to TheTechJournal.com users based on their visit to this and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

 **Use of Information Provided By User**  
We do not use the information provided by users, such as e-mail addresses and contents of e-mail, for any marketing purposes. Your personal information is not used by subsidiary organizations or businesses related to _[TheTechJournal.com](http://thetechjournal.com/)_ , unless clearly disclosed for specific situations.

 **Information Ownership**  
All e-mails, comments or other forms of communication received by _[TheTechJournal.com](http://thetechjournal.com/)_ are the property of _[TheTechJournal.com](http://thetechjournal.com/)_ and may be used for editorial or technical improvements to the Website at our discretion without any form of compensation being owed to the sender of said communications.

 **Information Security**  
We have appropriate security measures in our physical facilities and the facilities of our service providers to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our Website.

Information provided by Website visitors is held in confidence and used for editorial and technical improvements to the Website.

 **Privacy Contact**  
If you feel that this Website is not following this Privacy Policy, you may [contact us](https://thetechjournal.com/contact) at with your concerns.

 **Copyrights**  
Supreme caution has been taken to make sure that there are no copyright infringements in terms of the multimedia content and the subject matter that is posted in this blog. If you find anything that could be considered a violation of the copyright norms, please [contact us](https://thetechjournal.com/contact) immediately.
